import 'package:flutter/material.dart';
import 'package:qs_app/components/mcqs_content_box.dart';

class IssbMathContentScreen extends StatelessWidget {
  @override
  Widget build(BuildContext context) {
    return Scaffold(
      appBar: AppBar(
        title: Text('ISSB Math'),
      ),
      body: SingleChildScrollView(
        child: Padding(
          padding: EdgeInsets.all(20.0),
          child: Column(
            children: [

              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'What is the Sum of First 70 even Numbers?',
                option1: '4970',
                option2: '4950',
                option3: '4900',
                option4: '4980',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'a',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'The word Geometry has been derived from two Greek words:________?',
                option1: 'Geo means Earth',
                option2: 'Metron means Measurement',
                option3: 'Hence Geomatery means',
                option4: 'Earth measurement',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'd',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'What is the Sum of First 70 Odd Numbers?',
                option1: '4970',
                option2: '4960',
                option3: '4900',
                option4: '5000',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'c',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Express 1.09 in term of Percentage?',
                option1: '1.09%',
                option2: '10.9%',
                option3: '109%',
                option4: '1.10%',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'c',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Calculate the Average of 1,2,3,4,5?',
                option1: '1',
                option2: '3',
                option3: '4',
                option4: '5',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'b',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Find the Missing Number in the series 1, 6, 13, 22, 33?',
                option1: '36',
                option2: '40',
                option3: '46',
                option4: '56',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'c',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'One Gross is equal to_______?',
                option1: '5 Dozen',
                option2: '12 Dozen',
                option3: '15 Dozen',
                option4: '20 Dozen',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'b',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'A jogger running at 9 kmph alongside a railway track in 240 metres ahead of the engine of a 120 metres long train running at 45 kmph in the same direction. In how much time will the train pass the joɡɡer?',
                option1: '3.6 sec',
                option2: '18 sec',
                option3: '72 sec',
                option4: '36 sec',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'd',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Three flags each of different colours are available for a military exercise, Using these flags different codes can be generated by waving I. Single flag of different colours II. Any two flags in a different sequence of colours.III. three flags in a different sequence of colours.The maximum number of codes that can be generated is?',
                option1: '6',
                option2: '9',
                option3: '15',
                option4: '18',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'c',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Two trains are moving in opposite directions 60 km/hr and 90 km/hr. Their lengths are 1.10 km and 0.9 km respectively. The time taken by the slower train to cross the faster train in seconds is_____?',
                option1: '36',
                option2: '45',
                option3: '47',
                option4: '48',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'd',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Twelve inches equal to how many centimeters?',
                option1: '29',
                option2: '30.48',
                option3: '34.12',
                option4: '34.15',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'b',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Who is Called the Father of Calculus?',
                option1: 'Al-Khwarizmi',
                option2: 'Aristotle',
                option3: 'Herodotus',
                option4: 'Isaac Newton',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'd',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: '1 inch is equal to_______?',
                option1: '2.4 cm',
                option2: '2.5 cm',
                option3: '2.54 cm',
                option4: '3.54 cm',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'c',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'If the average marks of three batches of 55, 60 and 45 students respectively is 50, 55, 60, then the average marks of all the students is?',
                option1: '53.33',
                option2: '54.68',
                option3: '55',
                option4: '60',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'b',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'If a car is sold for Rs..50000 the profit is 17 percent, what would be profit percentage if sold for Rs. 47000?',
                option1: '14.85%',
                option2: '16.20%',
                option3: '14.50%',
                option4: '9.98%',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'd',
              ),


            ],
          ),
        ),
      ),
    );
  }
}


